(トビ)あれれ 先輩！
あんな所に団子屋がありますよ！
Oh, Senpai!
Over there...
There's a dango shop!
ちょっと休憩しましょうよ～。
Let's take a break.
We've been walking all day.
I'm exhausted!
You don't look exhausted at all.
ったく のんきなヤツだ。
Why are you so easygoing?
But Senpai, we're trying to
catch a Tailed Beast,
どこにいるのさえ
わからないんだから。
yet we don't even know where it is.
So let's just take it easy.
そういえば
何 捕まえるんでしたっけ？
By the way,
what are we going to catch again?
Three-Tails! Three-Tails!
一尾 ニ尾 ボクはトビ！ なんちって！
One-Tail, Two-Tails...
And I'm Tobi! Duh!
Here's dango for you.
お～！ うまそうだなぁ！
どれどれ～？
Wow! It looks yummy!
Let's see...
いただきま～す！
Munch time!
Man, it's so good!
This sauce is really good.
これは いいタレだ ハハッ！
甘すぎず辛すぎず。
It's not too sweet, nor too salty.
It's a masterpiece!
ん～！ 絶品ですよ これ！
あ～ おいしかった。
Ahh... It was great.
Oh, Senpai, Senpai. Look at that!
Huh?
That looks exactly like your work, doesn't it?
Could it be that your work is...
a rip-off?
You...!
(デイダラ)テメエ！
ギッ！
だぁ～っ！
I'm going to kill you!
(トビ)あ～れ～！
The Rampaging Tailed Beast
(牛頭)こ… これは!?
Th-This is...
(紅蓮)現れるよ 三尾が！
The Three-Tails is about to appear!
What's this feeling...?
What's the matter, Shino?
My insects...feel a weird Chakra.
Weird Chakra?
これまでに
感じたことがないような➡
They've never felt so much Chakra before.
膨大な量のチャクラだ。
(赤丸)ワン！
どうやら赤丸も お前の蟲と
同じものを感じてるようだぜ！
It looks like Akamaru feels
the same thing as your insects!
Then it must be there!
Let's hurry up.
(麟児)この感じ… この
ビリビリと空気を伝うような殺気…➡
This feeling... It's like highly charged air
and a frantic feeling...
木ノ葉のヤツら… じゃねえ。
This isn't from the guys
from the Hidden Leaf.
(麒児)何が起きてるんだ!?
What's happening?
Right there?!
What the heck is that?
A fog...?
(ヤマト)コウモリは
あの霧に向かって行ったようだね。
It looks like the bats are flying
toward the fog.
間違いない。 膨大なチャクラも
あそこから出ている。
No question about it!
A huge amount of Chakra
is coming from over there.
あの霧の中に いるってことか？
Is it inside that fog?
Yes, but we can't identify it.
あそこに突っ込んでみれば
わかるってばよ！
Let's dive in and find out!
まぁ そう焦るな…。
覚悟を決めるか。
Hey, slow down.
Let's get ready first.
ヘッ そうこなくっちゃ！
Heh! That's what I wanted to hear!
全員 戦闘準備！
しかし ムチャはするな。
Everyone, prepare for action!
But don't rush!
(シノ/キバ)了解！
ワン！
- Roger!
了解だってばよ！
Understood!
They're increasing in number.
援軍を呼んだか？
Did they call for reinforcements?
なんか
見つかりまくりなんだけど！
I think they can easily see us!
かまわん！ 一気に突っ込む！
It doesn't matter!
Let's drop in!
We're at a disadvantage number-wise.
ここは 紅蓮さんたちが戻るまで
時間稼ぎをするぞ。
Let's buy some time until
Guren gets here!
キホウ 煙幕をはれ！
(キホウ)あぁ 了解した。
Kihou, lay a smoke screen!
Understood.
カカシ先輩！
Kakashi Senpai!
A smoke screen...
They're lying in wait for us.
ここで時間を食えば➡
But if we stay here too long,
湖で何が起きているのか
探れなくなる可能性もある。
we won't be able to find out
what's happening at the lake.
二手に分かれるか…。
We should split into two groups...
ナルト お前は別行動だ。
え？ オレってば 戦わないのか？
Naruto, you go by yourself.
What?! I'm not attacking?
Our main mission is to research the lake.
Oh, that's right...
We'll create a diversion and
you head off to the center of the lake.
だが 戦闘は禁止だ。
あぁ わかった！
But don't attack.
Yes, understood.
Are you sure? Only Naruto...?
Let's show him a bit of trust.
《生き抜くことに関して
ナルトより勝負強いヤツはいない。
No one is a better survivor than Naruto.
頼むぞ ナルト。
Good luck, Naruto.
You're definitely
the Number One Unpredictable Ninja
in the Hidden Leaf.
反応がない。 誰もいないようだ。
No reaction...
It looks like nobody's here.
(カカシ)行くぞ！
Let's go!
(キバ)クソッ… なんも見えねえ。
Damn it! I can't see anything.
逃げたんでしょうか？
Did they escape already?
時間稼ぎかもしれん
油断するな！
They must be buying time.
Keep your guard up!
よし このへんからなら…！
All right, I think from here...
一気に湖に突っ込むってばよ！
I'm going to head into
the lake!
突っ込みすぎた…。
(ガマ竜)フフ おやつね。
I went in too deep...
Snack for me.
(ガマ吉)ったく 帰ったと思ったら
呼び出しおって！
Hey, right after we got home,
you called us over here!
ガマ使いが荒いのう オメエも！
You're such a toad driver!
Come on, I'll give you something in return.
しかし この強烈なチャクラ。
But, this intense Chakra...
I wonder what's behind the fog?
霧の向こうに
何がおるっちゅうんじゃ…。
(カブト)来るぞ！
It's coming!
これが三尾…。
This is the Three-Tails...
想像以上だ。
It's more than we expected...
なんだ？ この威圧感…。
What is this? This intimidation...!
(カブト)やった！ 成功だ！
We did it... It was a success.
幽鬼丸が三尾をコントロールしている！
Yuukimaru is controlling the Three-Tails!
うわ～！
幽鬼丸！
Yuukimaru!
まずい！ これ以上
力を使い続ければ…。
Damn! If he keeps using his power...!
(紅蓮)コイツが倒れたら
三尾は どうなる？
If he fails,
what will happen to the Three-Tails?
それを抑え込むのが
お前の役目だ！
Your job is to stop that from happening!
チッ！
《カブト : 幽鬼丸の力でも
三尾を抑えられないのか…》
Even Yuukimaru's power can't control
the Three-Tails...!
Yuukimaru!
何だってばよ!? この声は。
What's that sound?!
Guren!
Stop this beast immediately!
紅蓮 早く コイツの動きを封じろ！
Stop being so bossy!
いちいち命令するな！
This beast!
Although he's huge, he's quick!
《コイツ 図体のわりに
動きが早い！》
Right now!
今のうちに！
Gozu!
(紅蓮)牛頭！
(牛頭)早く！
Hurry!
(牛頭)うわぁ！
Crystal Style! Divine Pathway Jutsu!
どうだ！
There!
私の水晶が砕けた!?
My crystal shattered?!
チッ 結晶！ 巨大六角手裏剣！
Giant! Crystal Hexagonal Shuriken!
This is so hard!
Muddy turtle!
Guren! What are you doing?
≪(カブト)紅蓮 何やってる！
三尾を殺すつもりか!?
Are you trying to kill the Three-Tails?!
Contain him! Or we'll all die!
≪ヤツを封じ込めろ！
出来なければ 全滅するぞ！
Large-scale Jutsu need preparation!
《でかい術には それなりの
準備ってのがいるんだよ！》
It's too late!
《間に合わない！》
《牛頭！》
Gozu...!
Hurry...
晶遁！ 水晶壁 八の陣！
Crystal Style!
Crystal Wall, 8th Formation!
Eat this, turtle bastard!
(紅蓮)食らえ！ カメ野郎！
She did it...!
《晶遁… 紅蓮に
ここまで力があったとは》
Crystal Style...
I never knew Guren
had this much ability...
(紅蓮)ハァ ハァ… チャクラを…
使いすぎたか… ハァ ハァ…。
I used a bit too much...Chakra...
おい シノ 寄ってくんなよ。
Hey Shino,
don't get too close to me!
I wouldn't get too close to you.
(シノ)別に お前に
寄っているわけではない。
Then why did your shoulder brush
against me?!
(シノ)なぜなら オレたちの円陣が
小さくなっているからだ。
Because our circle is getting small.
ムダ口をたたくな！
Keep your mouth shut!
Focus on finding the enemy.
敵がどこにいるか
集中するんだ。
But, Kakashi Sensei!
でもよぉ カカシ先生！
Above us! Watch out!
(ヒナタ)上です 気をつけて。
《奇襲は失敗か》
Our ambush failed!
(サクラ)カカシ先生！
Kakashi Sensei!
サクラ サイ 助かったぞ。
Thanks Sakura, Sai.
Hinata, are you better already?
Yeah!
(シノ)それにしても よく…。
But still, how did she...?
(シノ)そうか 白眼か。
I see, her Byakugan...
We'd better be careful with
that little girl's Jutsu.
煙幕のなかだろうが
オレたちの居場所がバレちまう クソッ》
Even if we were in a smoke screen,
she would find us...
Damn it!
なんだ ここ？
波ひとつ立っとらんのぉ。
What kind of place is this?!
There's not one wave,
and no sign of fish.
魚の気配も まったくしない。
不気味じゃ。
It's really weird...
何か見えてきたぞ。
I see something.
(ガマ竜)ああ カメさんだ。
カメさんがいるよ。
Oh! It's a turtle!
There's a turtle inside!
(ガマ竜)兄ちゃん
なんだろうね このカメさん？
Brother! What kind of turtle is this?
ナ ナルト コイツは尾獣じゃ。
尾獣？
Na-Naruto, th-this is a Tailed Beast!
Tailed Beast?
(ガマ吉)じゃけん 三尾じゃ！
Yeah! It's the Three-Tails!
ウゥ…。
三尾？
Three-Tails...?
(三尾)オォ…。
オォ～ッ！
《あれだけの術でも
止められないのか》
Even that huge Jutsu couldn't stop it?!
紅蓮 幽鬼丸を連れて逃げろ。
牛頭 お前もだ。
Guren! Take Yuukimaru and run!
Gozu! You, too!
牛頭 幽鬼丸を守れ！
わかりました。
Gozu, protect Yuukimaru!
All right!
紅蓮さん。
Guren...!
お前の相手は 私だよ！ ハアッ！
You fight with me!
アイツは！
She's...!
なんで アイツが三尾と？
Why is she fighting with the Three-Tails?!
ヤァ～ッ！
Guren!
紅蓮さん！
なんで お前がここに？
What are you doing here...?!
まさか。
Don't tell me...
((ボクを思ってくれる人が
いるところが ボクの帰る場所))
Where there's someone thinking of me,
that's where I go home to.
帰るべき場所ってのは
アイツらのとこかよ！
His place to return is...
with them?!
なめるな ドロガメ！
Don't underestimate me...
Muddy turtle!
紅蓮さん！
Guren!
((紅蓮 : この椿は
決して枯れはしない。
This camellia will never wither.
(私が死なないかぎりはな))
As long as I'm alive.
Guren...
Gozu...!
(紅蓮)牛頭。
What are you doing?!
Take Yuukimaru and...
get out of here!
紅蓮さん…。
Guren...
ボク 帰る所が見つかったんだ。
I figured out where to return home to.
お前…。
You...
ゴオッ！
なんじゃ… 動きが止まったぞ。
What?! The Three-Tails
has stopped moving.
まさか…。
(ガマ吉)
アイツ 三尾をコントロールできるのか!?
(カカシ)何だ？
(ヤマト)カカシ先輩！
あれは…。
なんだと!?
《紅蓮 : あれは
三尾が現れた異空間!?
あれに飲み込まれたら…》
((大丈夫か？
(あったかい))
((幽鬼丸 : はい。
(紅蓮)お前 これは…))
《紅蓮 : 幽鬼丸…》
(紅蓮)
すべてのチャクラを この術に…。
今度は
ボクが手を握っててあげる…。
へ～ 知らなかった。
サイって 私たちより
一つ年上なのね。
ゲジマユと一緒か…。
うわっ！ ヤマト隊長って
あれで 26歳!?
えっ！ あんなオヤジ顔なのに…。
趣味は 建築関係の本を読むこと。
うわ… 暗えな…。
えっ？
ハハッ！ 隊長と イルカ先生って
同い歳だぜ。
ホントだ。 やだ…
趣味は 湯治って…。
ギャハハ… まるで ジジイだな。
ところで サクラちゃん 知ってた？
シズネのねえちゃん 31だぜ。
えっ それは… 思ったより…。
だろ だろ… そうなると あの➡
アヒィ～っていうリアクション
ムリしすぎじゃねえ？
シ… シズネのねえちゃん!!
(シズネ)今の話
もう一度 聞きたいな。
フッ！
アヒィ～!!